Guide to the King County Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- King County Labor Council records, 1970-2003; 1990-2000; 1940-002; 20.00 cubic ft. 20 boxes
  The Administrative Records series include minutes from 1987-1997 and financial statements from 1982-1999. There also is Correspondence with Affiliated Unions from 1983-2003, including Service Employees, Teamsters, and United Food and Commercial Workers. The Subject Series includes information about labor related topics as well as correspondence with non-affiliated organizations from 1970-2002. The Committee on Political Education series includes mailings and subject files on political candidates from 1992-1999.
  Records in the Council's custody following the earlier gift in 1969 are believed to have been destroyed.
  Donated in 2004.
  Open to all users.
  - SERIES I: ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
    - Subseries A: Minutes, 1987-1997 (Box-folder 1/1- 1/20)
      - 1997 Executive Board and Eve. Meeting Minutes (Box-folder 1/1)
      - 1997 Executive Board and Eve. Meeting Minutes (Box-folder 1/2)
      - 1996 Meetings/Notes (Box-folder 1/3)
      - 1996 Meetings/Notes (Box-folder 1/4)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1995 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1995 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1994 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1994 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1993 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1993 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1993 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1992 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1992 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1992 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1991 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - King County Central Labor Council Executive Board and Minutes 1991 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1990 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1989 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1988 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - King County Central Labor Council Minutes 1987 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Subseries B: Affiliate Correspondence, [?1970--1999?] (Box-folder 2/1-7/3)
      - Aerospace Machinists Local 751 1995-1999 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Aerospace Machinists Local 751 1992-1994 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Aerospace Machinists Local 751 1970-1991 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Aerospace Machinists Strike Support Group 1995 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Air Line Pilots Association International, 1988-1998 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Air Transport District 143 1992- 95, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Air Transport 1351 1985-91, 1985- 1991 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Air Transport 2202 1993-99, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance 1992-1999 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Automotive Machinists 289 1988- 96, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers' Int'l #9 1989-1997 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Boilermakers 104 1976-1998 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Boilermakers Local 502 1993-95, 1993- 1995 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Bricklayers 1/WA 1988-1997 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters Local 13, 1987-99, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters Local 1797, 1985-96, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Pacific Northwest District Council of Carpenters 1985- 99, 1985-1998 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - United Brotherhood of Carpenters (UBC) 1144, 1986- 98, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Carpenters - Lumber and Sawmill Workers Local 2633, 1985-99, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Carpet, Linoleum and Soft Tile Layers Local 1238, 1989- 98, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Cement Masons Local 528, 1986-99, 1986- 1999 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Coalition of Labor Union Women 1988-99, 1988- 1999 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Communications Workers of America Local 7800, 1991-99, 1991- 1999 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Communications Workers Local 7800, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Communications Workers of America Local 7803, 1985-87, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Communications Workers Local 9400, 1990- 2003 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - AFSCME 21, 1992-97, 1992- 1997 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - County and City Employees Local 21, 1984-91, 1984- 1991 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - County and City Employees Local 2083, 1987-96, 1987- 1996 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - County and City Employees Local 2083C, 1984-98, 1984- 1998 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Deep Sea Fisherman's Union/SUP, 2002 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Electrical Workers Local 46, 1993-98, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Electrical Workers Local 46, 1985- 98, 1985-1998 (Box-folder 2/33)
      - Electrical Workers Local 77, 1985-96, 1985- 1996 (Box-folder 2/34)
      - Electrical Workers Local 89, 1990-99, 1990- 1999 (Box-folder 2/35)
      - IUE Local 1002, 1989-95, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 2/36)
      - International Union of Elevator Constructors 19, 1992-97, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 2/37)
      - Seattle Fire Fighters Union Local 27, 1985- 98, 1985-1998 (Box-folder 2/38)
      - International Association of Fire Fighters Local 1257 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Fire Fighters Local 1352, 1988 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Fire Fighters Local 2024 (New Affiliate 3/98 - Never Paid Dues), 1998 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Association of Flight Attendants Local 10, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Association of Flight Attendants Local 17, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Association of Flight Attendants Local 19, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Garment Workers Local 17, 1989- 1995 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Garment Workers (Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees) Local 184, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Glass Workers Local 50, 1988- 1993 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers Local 87, 1988- 1998 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Glaziers, Architectural Metal and Glassworkers Local 188, 1986-94, 1986- 1994 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - American Federation of Government Employees Local 40, 1991-92, 1991- 1992 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - American Federation of Government Employees Local 1170, 1988-95, 1988- 1995 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - American Federation of Government Employees Local 3197, 1988-99, 1988- 1999 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Graphic Communications Union Local 767M, 1988- 1998 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Graphic Communications Union Local 767 M District Council (DC) 2, 1985- 1999 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HERE) Local 8 (1 of 3) 1985-95, 1985- 1995 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HERE) Local 8 (2 of 3) 1993-96, 1993- 1996 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HERE) Local 8 (3 of 3) 1995-99, 1995- 1999 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HERE) Local 8 Organizing Project Expenses, 1997 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HERE) Local 8/King County Organizing Project (1 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Hotel and Restaurant Employees (HERE) Local 8/King County Organizing Project (2 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Inlandboatmen's Union of the Pacific (IBU), 1985- 99, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Iron Workers Local 86, 1990-98, 1990- 1998 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Iron Workers Local 509, 1988-97, 1988- 1997 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - King County Union Retirees Council, 1992,94, 1992, 1994 (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1996-99, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Public Service and Industrial Employees Local 1239, 1987-94, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA) Local 242, 1984-94, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC) Local 79, 1988-96, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - International Longshore and Warehouse Union (ILWU) Local 9, 1989-98, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union (ILWU) Local 19, 1989-98, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 3/32)
      - International Associaiton of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) Local 79, 1988-99, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 3/33)
      - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW) Local 282, 1999 (Box-folder 3/34)
      - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM) Local 1103, 1991 (Box-folder 3/35)
      - Maritime Trades Department, 1991- 98, 1991-1998 (Box-folder 3/36)
      - Masters, Mates, and Pilots Union (MM+P), Pacific Maritime Region, 1984-93, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 3/37)
      - Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (MEBA) District 1, PCD, 1987-99, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 3/38)
      - Puget Sound Metal Trades Council, 1984- 97, 1984-1997 (Box-folder 3/39)
      - Millmen's Union Local 338, 1984-93, 1984- 1993 (Box-folder 3/40)
      - Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers (GMPP+AW) Local 158, 1988 (Box-folder 3/41)
      - Moving Picture Machine Operators Local 154, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Moving Picture Machine Operators Local 175, 1989-1995 (Box-folder 4/2)
      - American Federation of Musicians 76- 493, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 4/3)
      - NFL Players Association (Seattle Seahawks), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Pacific Northwest Newspaper Guild Local 82, 1987-1998 (Box-folder 4/5)
      - OPEIU Local 8 re: El Centro de la Raza, 1997- 1999 (Box-folder 4/6)
      - OPEIU Local 8 1996-99 Part 1 of 3, 1996- 1999 (Box-folder 4/7)
      - OPEIU Local 8 1996-99 Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 4/8)
      - OPEIU Local 8 1996-99 Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 4/9)
      - OPEIU Local 8 1991-95, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 4/10)
      - OPEIU Local 8 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/11)
      - OPEIU Local 8 1983-88, 1983- 1988 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Operating Engineers Local 286, 1984- 1999 (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Operating Engineers Local 609, 1982- 1999 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Painters District Council 5, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Painters Local 33, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - Painters and Allied Trades Local 1094, 1984-1998 (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Plasterers' Union Local 77, 1986- 1998 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Plumbers Union Local 32, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 5/2)
      - Port Angeles/Puget Sound Pilots, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5/3)
      - Greater Seattle Area Postal Workers Union (GSALAPWU), 1987-1999 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Pride at Work, 1997- 1999 (Box-folder 5/5)
      - Print Trades Council of Washington and Oregon, 1985- 1998 (Box-folder 5/6)
      - Professional and Technical Engineers Local 17, 1984- 1999 (Box-folder 5/7)
      - Puget Sound Council of Senior Citizens, 1988- 1999 (Box-folder 5/8)
      - Sailors' Union of the Pacific, 1984-1998 (Box-folder 5/9)
      - Seafarers' International Union, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 5/10)
      - The Building Trades Residential/Commerical Enhancement Program, Undated (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Seattle/King County Building and Construction Trades Council 1994-1999 (Box-folder 5/12)
      - Seattle/King County Building and Construction Trades Council 1973-1993 (Box-folder 5/13)
      - Public Safety Employees Local 519, 1987- 1996 (Box-folder 5/14)
      - Service Employees Local 6 1993-1999 (Box-folder 5/15)
      - Service Employees Local 6 1989-1992 (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Service Employees Local 6 1984-1988 (Box-folder 5/17)
      - Service Employees Local 925, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 5/18)
      - Service Employees Local 1199, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 5/19)
      - Service Employees Local 1199 Group Health Negotiations, 1995 (Box-folder 5/20)
      - Service Employees Local 1199 Hospitals and Healthcare 1989-1992 (Box-folder 5/21)
      - Service Employees 1199/Providence Health System, 1999 (Box-folder 5/22)
      - Service Employees 1199 Virginia Mason Nurses 1998 (Box-folder 5/23)
      - Service Employees 1199/West SEattle Psychiatric Hospital, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 5/24)
      - Service Employees State Council, 2000- 2003 (Box-folder 5/25)
      - Sheet Metal Workers Local 66, 1984- 1991 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Stage Hands Local 15, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 5/27)
      - Sprinkler Fitters Local 699, 1973-2000 (Box-folder 5/28)
      - State Employees Local 1488, 1985- 1998 (Box-folder 5/29)
      - State Employees Local 304, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 5/30)
      - State Employees Local 435, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 5/31)
      - State Employees Local 843, 1988- 1998 (Box-folder 6/1)
      - Steelworkers Local 7945, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 6/2)
      - Community College Teachers Local 1789 (Federal Way), 1987-1999 (Box-folder 6/3)
      - Teamsters Local 117, 1997- 1998 (Box-folder 6/4)
      - Teamsters Local 174 1997-1999 (Box-folder 6/5)
      - Teamsters Local 174 1988-1996 (Box-folder 6/6)
      - Teamsters Local 174 - Browning-Ferris Industries (BFI), 1995- 1996 (Box-folder 6/7)
      - Teamsters Local 763, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 6/8)
      - Television and Radio Artists, Seattle Local, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 6/9)
      - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 587, 1984-1999 (Box-folder 6/10)
      - Amalgamated Transit Union Local 1384, 1984-1993 (Box-folder 6/11)
      - United Farm Workers Strawberry Campaign, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 6/12)
      - United Farm Workers of Washington State, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 6/13)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers District Council 17, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 6/14)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 1001, 1975- 1982 (Box-folder 6/15)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 1001, 1983- 1988 (Box-folder 6/16)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 1001, 1989- 1991 (Box-folder 6/17)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 1001, 1992- 2001 (Box-folder 6/18)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 1105, 1982- 1989 (Box-folder 6/19)
      - United Food and Commercial Workesrs 1105, 1990- 1999 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - UFCW 1001 Evergreen General Hospital Med Center Bond Issue, 1988 (Box-folder 6/21)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 1182, 1978-1998 (Box-folder 6/22)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 141 - United Staff Nurses Union, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 6/23)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 554, 1988-1999 (Box-folder 6/24)
      - United Food and Commercial Workers 81, 1984- 1999 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - Subseries C: Financial Statements, 1982- 1999 (Box-folder 7/1-7/2)
  - SERIES II: SUBJECT SERIES
    - King County Central Labor Council Financial Statements 1990-1999 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - King County Central Labor Council FInancial Statements 1982-1989 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Affirmative Action, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Agreement Dynamics, 1990- 1996 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Alaska Fishermen's Union, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Alliance for Education, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - American Income Life Insurance, 1997- 1998 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Apprenticeship Opportunities, 1992- 2000 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - African American Union Organizations, 1992- 1998 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Boy Scouts of Amercia, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Breakfast Group, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Seattle Burma Ordinance, 1994- 1998 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Communications Workers of America / Shuttle Express, 1998 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Cherry Pint (Gateway Pacific Terminal), 1994-1999 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Church/Labor Coalition, Labor in the Pulpits, 1999 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Church-Labor-Community Forum, 1993- 1996 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Coalition of City Unions 1994-1997 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Coalition of City Unions 1994-1997 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Confluence (Conference), 1999 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - Costco, 1993- 1997 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Northwest Rail Project, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - Duwamish Coalition Part 3 (1 of 2), 1995-1997 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Duwamish Coalition Part 3 (2 of 2), 1994- 1995 (Box-folder 7/24)
    - Duwamish Coalition Part 2 (1 of 2), 1994- 1995 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Duwamish Coalition Part 2 (2 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Duwamish Coalition Part 1 (1 of 2), 1994 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Duwamish Coalition Part 1 (2 of 2), 1994- 1995 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Duwamish Plan, 2000 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Duwamish Speeches and Briefings, 1995 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Economic Development Council of Seattle and King County (1 of 2), 1996-2000 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - Economic Development Council of Seattle and King County (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - Economic Opportunity Institute (1 of 2), 1999- 2000 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Economic Opportunity Institute (1 of 2), 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Economic Security Institute, 1998 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - King County Central Labor Council Education Committee, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - El Centro de la Raza, 1994- 1997 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Emerald Downs (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Emerald Downs (2 of 2), 1993-1996 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Freight Action Strategy (FAST) Corridor, 1997 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - Fast Track Trade Legislation (1 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Fast Track Trade Legislation (2 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Federal Legislation: Wards Cove Workers Act, 1992 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Federal Way Schools - Site Leadership Team, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Football Northwest Inc. Stadium, 1997 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Freeway Hall Case, 1987- 1993 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Global Mariner, 1999 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Anti-Labor Arguments: G.O.P. Attacks, 1996 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Governor Gary Locke, 1998 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - Governor's Appointments, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Group Health/United Unions Part 1, 1992- 1997 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - Group Health/United Unions Part 2, 1992- 1997 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - Group Health/United Unions Part 3, 1992- 1997 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - United Unions (Box-folder 9/12)
    - Guatemala/Starbucks, 1992- 1999 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Herzmark, Jay (Safety and Health), 1998 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - International Longshore and Warehouse Union, 1998 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Services, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Independent Media Center, c. 2000 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Industrial Areas Foundation, 1998 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Institute for a Democratic Future, 2000 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Institute for Economic Security, 1997 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - International Labor Communications Association (Scanner), 1993-1997 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - International Visitors, 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - International Women's Day, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - International Workers of the World Local 660, Undated (Box-folder 9/24)
    - Jobs with Justice (1 of 2), 1997- 1998 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Jobs with Justice (2 of 2), 1993-1996 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Kent Unions, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - King County Alternative Dispute Resolution Services, 1998 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - King County Contingent Work Task Force, 1999 (Box-folder 9/29)
    - King County Corrections Guild, 1997 (Box-folder 9/30)
    - King County Council - Partnership vs. Privatization, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 9/31)
    - King County International Trade Initiative Board (1 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box-folder 9/32)
    - King County International Trade Initiative Board (2 of 2), 1997 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - King County Labor Summit, 1998- 1999 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - King County Living Wage Proposal, 1998 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - King County Organizing Project, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - King County Regional Wastewater Service Plan, 1999 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - King County Transportation Coalition, 1999 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - King County Unions Coalition, 1994- 1999 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Korean Labor Movement, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - KCLC Labor Agency United Way Budget, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - KCLC Labor Agency Sheet Metal Contract, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - KCLC Labor Agency/Worker Center Fiscal Sponsorship Agreement, 1996 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Labor Day Journal, 1993, 1996 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Labor, Environment, and Social Justice, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Labor History Month, 1993 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Labor and Industries - ABC/AGC Lawsuits, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Labor Mural/Judkins Park, 1998 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Labor Party, 1993- 1999 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - Labor Studies - Highline Community College, 1996 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Labor's Heritage, 1997 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Land Use Study Group, 1995 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Landmarks Preservation Board, 1998 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - League of Women Voters, 1994- 1998 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Livable Washington (1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Livable Washington (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Living Wage (1 of 2), 2000- 2002 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Living Wage (2 of 2), 1996-1999 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Lockheed, 1987 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - Low Income Housing Institute, 1995- 1997 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Maddy, 1996 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Maritime Alliance of the Pacific Northwest, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Maritime: United States Longshoremen and Harborworkers, 1993 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Maritime Museum, 1995 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Membership Education and Mobilization for Organizing 1996 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Membership Education and Mobilization for Organizing 1996 (2 of 2), 1994, 1996 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - MEMO - Train the Trainer, 1996 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - MEMO Training 1994 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Metro Apprenticeship Guidelines, 1993 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Metro Council, 1993 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Metropolitan Parks District, 1999 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - (United) Mine Workers Association, 1993 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Minimum Wage 1996 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Senator Patty Murray, 1996 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (1 of 7), 1994 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (2 of 7), 1993 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (3 of 7), 1993 (Box-folder 11/19)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (4 of 7), 1993 (Box-folder 11/20)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (5 of 7), 1992 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (6 of 7), 1988-1991 (Box-folder 11/22)
    - NAFTA (Including Fast Track, Fair Trade, etc.) (7 of 7), 1991 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - NAFTA - Transitional Adjustment Assistance, 1993 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - National Interfaith Committee for Worker Justice, 1997 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - National Partnership for Community Investment, 1993 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - National Planning Association, 1992, 1994 (Box-folder 12/5)
    - National Political Congress of Black Women, 1995 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Neighborhood Funders Group, 1997 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Neutrality/Check Card Agreements, 1999 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - New Party, 1997, 2001 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Northwest Alternatives, Undated (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Northwest Area Foundation, 1995 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Northwest Center for Progressive Research, 1995 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Northwest Labor Arts Festival - 1995 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Northwest Labor Arts Project (Teach-in Folklife) 1997 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Northwest Rail Corridor, 1995 (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Operating Engineers Local 701, 1994 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Oregon Farm Workers, 1997 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - KCLC Organizing Committee 1996 (Box-folder 12/18)
    - KCLC Organizing Committee 1994- 1997 (Box-folder 12/19)